http://www.mdsbattery.co.uk/terms.html

InformationAbout MDS BatteryContact MDS BatteryNeed Help?DeliveryWarrantyBattery RecyclingMDS Battery BlogTerms & ConditionsPrivacy & Cookie Policy          Space at the bottom of the menuTerms & ConditionsBelow you'll find our full Ts & Cs - the legal bit that we have to make clear - but please remember we are human and if a mistake has happened or something has gone wrong, please give us a call or drop us an email in the first instance.If you call us during office hours (Monday - Friday, 9.00AM - 5.00PM), your call will be answered promptly and we'll deal with any issues you have immediately; out of hours, send us an email and we'll get back to you once we are open.Call us free on 0800 310 2100 or email sales@mdsbattery.co.ukFull contact details here Mistakes, Complaints & DisputesConsumer LawMDS will meet its obligations under the Consumer Protection Laws currently in force.Faulty GoodsIf goods are faulty or different from those ordered MDS will make a full refund - this refund will be made as soon as possible or at the latest within 30 days of agreeing to give the refund - see separate returns policy.Mistakes in bills, receipts or paymentsMDS undertakes to correct any mistakes in bills, receipts or payments as soon as possible and at the latest within 30 days of agreement to do so.Complaints/DisputesMDS has an effective system for handling complaints/disputes and we will:a. Acknowledge complaints within 5 working days.b. Advise you how long it will take to resolve the complaint.c. Keep you fully informed throughout the process. Data Protection & PrivacyData Protection ActMDS will meet the conditions of the Data Protection Act 2018 (DPA).Privacy PolicyThe consumer has the option to withhold personal information, which is not needed for the transaction. All information relating to the transaction will be collected and stored by MDS. MDS will not collect sensitive personal information without the explicit consent of the consumer (for example, health or ethnic origin).MDS will allow customers easy access to their own personal information and ensure it is accurate and up to date. Information is collected during the registration and purchasing processes and is used in order to facilitate swift delivery of goods ordered through the site. MDS also undertakes to tell the consumer if it going to transfer personal information outside the European Economic Area.You will not receive any marketing material from MDS unless you specifically state that you wish to receive it, at the point of registration. If you decide that you wish to receive marketing material but later change your mind, you may unsubscribe from the newsletter by sending an e-mail to newsletter@mdsbattery.co.uk, entering UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line.The person responsible for privacy matters is: Michael Field - Managing DirectorAll information is collected lawfully and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 2018Security policyMDS undertakes to ensure that their web site is secure so that consumers' personal information and transactions remain confidential and cannot be interfered with and that the content of the MDS site cannot be interfered with. The person responsible for security matters is: Michael Field - Managing Director.Cookie policyOur complete Cookie policy is available click here Customer SupportOur customer support and service telephone number is: 0800 310 2100 and is available 09:00 hrs to 17:15 hrs Monday to Friday. Calls are free of charge to the 0800 number.  Returns PolicyMDS are committed to ensuring that you are completely happy with your purchase; however if you are not satisfied or have a problem, please follow the following returns procedures. You have the right to cancel under the Distance Selling Regulations (full details below).We do not supply goods on a trial basis and after this “cooling off” period goods can only be returned if they are faulty. If faulty goods are returned within 30 days we will replace or refund as appropriate, after 30 days we will repair or replace under the terms of our warranty.Please contact us prior to returning goods to obtain a “Returns Authorisation Number” and ensure this is clearly marked on the parcel when goods are returned; if goods are returned without an RAN number delays in processing may occur. Please keep all materials and packaging in case goods need to be returned and ensure that any goods are sent back in the same condition that you received them. You are liable for the cost of return carriage except in the case of goods that are supplied incorrectly or faulty in which case we will refund you the reasonable return carriage costs. If you have any further queries regarding our return policy please contact us.  Distance Selling RegulationsUnder the Distance Selling Regulations, you have the right to cancel the contract for any reason within 14 working days after the date you receive the goods. The cancellation notice must be given in writing by letter, fax, email or any other durable medium.MDS Battery Limited1 Riverwalk Business ParkJeffreys RoadEnfieldEN3 7QNPhone - 0800 310 2100 / 01992 707030Fax – 01992 707031Email – sales@mdsbattery.co.ukOnce you have cancelled the order you have a duty of care for the goods and it is your responsibility to return them to us; returns costs are at your expense and we recommend the use of an insured trackable service.We will refund you in full as soon as possible after we receive the returned goods and, in any event, within 30 days of receipt of the notice of cancellation. The refund will be for the full amount paid including the delivery cost. The only exceptions are goods that are made to your own specification or personalised.GuaranteeNew goods are guaranteed for a period of 1 year from date of purchase on a return to base basis.This is in addition to the Consumers' statutory rights.  DeliveryWe will undertake to deliver within 30 days unless mutually agreed otherwise but would normally expect to despatch ex stock within 24 hours - Monday to Friday.If for any reason we cannot fulfil the order within this period we will inform you by email.   Site About MDS Delivery Terms & Conditions Privacy & Cookie Policy Battery Recycling Site MapNavigate CSB Industrial Batteries Yuasa Motorcycle Batteries Yuasa Car Batteries Replacement UPS Batteries Mobility Scooter BatteriesTrade Customers Trade and volume buyers, please call us on 0800 310 2100   Government, Education and Corporate purchase orders welcomeContact Contact MDS Need Help? Read The MDS Blog Copyright MDS Battery 2020                                  ALL PRODUCTSMotorcycle BatteriesYuasa 6V BatteriesYuasa 12V BatteriesYuasa YTX BatteriesYuasa YTZ BatteriesYuasa GYZ BatteriesShorai Lithium BatteriesOdyssey Racing BatteriesMotorcycle Battery ChargersBattery ChargersAnsmann ChargersCTEK Battery ChargersMobility ChargersOptimate Battery ChargersSterling Battery ChargersOther ChargersCar BatteriesYuasa YBX3000 RangeYuasa YBX5000 RangeYuasa YBX7000 RangeYuasa YBX9000 RangeYuasa JIS RangeCar Battery ChargersOdyssey BatteriesOdyssey Extreme BatteriesLeisure BatteriesNumax Leisure BatteriesYuasa YBX Active BatteriesElectric VehiclesElectric Bike BatteriesMobility Scooter BatteriesRazor Scooter BatteriesUPS BatteriesReplacement RBC KitsReplacement MGE KitsReplacement Delta Power KitsUPS Battery KitsPLC BatteriesFor Allen BradleyFor FanucFor GE FanucFor MitsubishiFor ModiconFor OmronFor SiemensFor Texas InstrumentsOther PLC BatteriesIndustrial BatteriesCSB EVX & EVH SeriesCSB GP & GPL SeriesCSB HR SeriesCSB HRL SeriesCSB XHRL SeriesCSB TPL SeriesCSB UPS SeriesOdyssey BatteriesYuasa IndustrialAnsmann Li-ion PacksEmergency LightingEnersys CyclonClearance StockClearance StockMarine PowerMarine ChargersBattery to Battery ChargersMarine ElectricsMains InvertersMarine BatteriesYuasa YBX ActiveMarine ElectronicsYacht DevicesHousehold BatteriesDuracellAnsmannRechargeablesTorches & WorklightsTorches & WorklightsInformationAbout MDSContact MDSBattery RecyclingTerms & ConditionsHelp & SupportNeed Help?DeliveryPrivacy & CookiesBlogMDS Battery BlogUPS BATTERIESReplacement UPS Battery KitsAPC RBC Replacement Battery KitsDelta Power Replacement Battery KitsMGE Replacement Battery KitsOther UPS Replacement Battery KitsBest Selling UPS Battery KitsMDS48/RBC48 Replacement Battery KitMDS7/RBC7 Replacement Battery KitMDS12/RBS12 Replacement Battery KitMDS43/RBC43 Replacement Battery KitInformationReplacement UPS Battery KitsBattery RecyclingHelp & SupportNeed Help?DeliveryINDUSTRIAL BATTERIESCSB BatteriesCSB EVX & EVH Series BatteriesCSB GP & GPL Series BatteriesCSB HR Series BatteriesCSB HRL Series BatteriesCSB XHRL Series BatteriesCSB TPL Series BatteriesCSB UPS Series BatteriesYuasa BatteriesYuasa Industrial BatteriesEmergency Lighting PacksOdyssey BatteriesOdyssey Extreme BatteriesEnersys CyclonEnersys Cyclon BatteriesAnsmann Li-Ion PacksAnsmann Li-Ion Battery PacksElectric VehiclesElectric Bike BatteriesMobility Scooter BatteriesRazor Scooter BatteriesReplacement UPS Battery KitsAPC RBC Battery KitsMGE Battery KitsOther UPS Battery KitsBest SellersCSB GP1272 Lead Acid BatteryCSB HR1221W Lead Acid BatteryCSB HR1234W Lead Acid BatteryCSB EVX12200 Cyclic BatteryCSB UPS12460 Lead Acid BatteryOdyssey PC680 Extreme BatteryYuasa NP7-12 VRLA BatteryRBC7 Replacement UPS KitInformationCSB Ranges ExplainedBattery RecyclingHelp & SupportNeed Help?DeliveryMOTORCYCLE BATTERIESYuasa Motorcycle BatteriesYuasa 6V Motorcycle BatteriesYuasa 12V Motorcycle BatteriesYuasa YTX MF Motorcycle BatteriesYuasa YTZ Motorcycle BatteriesYuasa GYZ Motorcycle BatteriesShorai Motorcycle BatteriesShorai Lithium Motorcycle BatteriesOdyssey BatteriesOdyssey Extreme BatteriesBattery ChargersCTEK Battery ChargersOptimate Battery ChargersShorai Lithium ChargerBest SellersYuasa YTX9-BS BatteryYuasa YTX12-BS BatteryYuasa YTX14-BSYuasa YT12B-BS BatteryYuasa YTZ10S BatteryShorai LFX14L2-BS12 LithiumInformationYuasa Ranges ExplainedShipping Battery AcidHelp & SupportNeed Help?DeliveryCAR BATTERIESYuasa Car BatteriesYuasa YBX3000 Car BatteriesYuasa YBX5000 Car BatteriesYuasa YBX7000 Car BatteriesYuasa YBX9000 Car BatteriesYuasa JIS Series Car BatteriesOdyssey BatteriesOdyssey Extreme BatteriesCar Battery ChargersAnsmann Battery ChargersCTEK Battery ChargersOptimate Battery ChargersBest SellersYuasa YBX5063 Car BatteryYuasa YBX9096 Car BatteryYuasa YBX5100 Car BatteryYuasa YBX5110 Car BatteryYuasa YBX5019 Car BatteryYuasa YBX7100 Car BatteryInformationYuasa Car Battery RangesChoosing The Right Car BatteryWinter Car Battery MaintenanceHelp & SupportNeed Help?DeliveryPLC BATTERIESPLC BatteriesPLC Batteries for Allen BradleyPLC Batteries for FanucPLC Batteries for GE FanucPLC BatteriesPLC Batteries for MitsubishiPLC Batteries for ModiconPLC Batteries for OmronPLC BatteriesPLC Batteries for SiemensPLC Batteries for Texas InstrumentsOther PLC BatteriesPopular PLC BatteriesMitsubishi PLC Battery CR17335SE-MCGE Fanuc PLC Battery B9712TAllen Bradley PLC Battery B9650TMitsubishi PLC Battery B9670MCOmron PLC Battery B9650BHelp & SupportNeed Help?DeliveryMARINE & LEISUREMarine and Leisure PowerSterling Power Marine and Leisure Battery ChargersSterling Power Battery to Battery ChargersMarine and Leisure ElectricsSterling Power Mains InvertersMarine and Leisure BatteriesMarine and Leisure BatteriesYuasa YBX Active Marine and Leisure BatteriesMarine ElectronicsYacht Devices Marine ElectronicsCONTACTContact MDS BatteryContact DetailsNeed Help?DeliveryWarrantyInformationAbout MDSBattery RecyclingTerms & ConditionsPrivacy & Cookie PolicyMDS Battery BlogAll PostsIndustrial Battery PostsUPS Battery PostsMotorcycle Battery PostsCar Battery PostsMarine Power PostsLocationAddressMDS Battery Limited1 Riverwalk Business ParkJeffreys RoadEnfieldEN3 7QNPhone 0800 310 2100  View Basket | New Account | Sign In
